videos4download.com 2011-11-08

# Privacy Policy

### Information Collection and Use 

  * MultiMedia collects personal information when you register with MultiMedia, when you use MultiMedia products or services, when you visit MultiMedia pages or the pages of certain MultiMedia partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. MultiMedia may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. Once you register with MultiMedia and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * MultiMedia collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer. 
  * MultiMedia automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, MultiMedia cookie information, and the page you request. 
  * MultiMedia uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 
  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * MultiMedia does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under special circumstances 

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences 

  * You can edit your MultiMedia Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. 
  * New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MultiMedia service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the MultiMedia Newsletter, that are considered part of your MultiMedia account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

### Confidentiality and Security 

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 
  * Your MultiMedia Account Information is password-protected. 
  * In certain areas MultiMedia uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * MultiMedia may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MultiMedia account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

### Questions and Suggestions 

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a [ feedback form](http://www.multimedia.com.ro/contact.html) or you can contact us at: 

Multimedia SRL  
Mobile: +(40-745) 526 896  
E-mail: [ office@multimedia.com.ro](mailto:office@multimedia.com.ro)

If you see unauthorized or illegal materials on this website, please send an e-mail to: [ office@multimedia.com.ro](mailto:office@multimedia.com.ro) __
